# **RIKKE BLOM THØGERSEN**



I specialise in online communication, and take pride in constructing well-produced written and visual texts. Over the last couple of years, layout, web development and graphic design have become some of my favorite genres.

I enjoy working in dynamic teams with room for both personal initiative and exchange of ideas.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Danish, native speaker English, fluent written & spoken German, beginner

## **CONTACT**



+45 28763312



rikke\_blom@hotmail.com



Peter Bangs Vej 161 2000 Frederiksberg

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020	Student Assistant, KEA Facility    consumer behaviour    nudging    Microsoft Excel
2017	Communication Intern, Odense Municipality    SoMe    websites    event planning    graphic design    administration       newsletters
2012-2013	Pedagogical assistant, Assens Municipality
2008-2012	Sales Assistant, Tommerup Kiosk

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

2016-2019	Boardmember, Erasmus Student Network Odense
	Communication Manager & Secretary
	$\  \operatorname{SoMe} \  \operatorname{event} \operatorname{planning} \  \operatorname{blogging} \  \operatorname{newsletters} \  \operatorname{photography} \  \operatorname{coordination}$
	of volunteers    minute taking    travel guide    administration
2015-2016	Active Member, Erasmus Student Network Odense     SoMe    event planning    blogging    newsletter    photography
2010-2016	Youth Camp coordinator, Cultural Village Tommerup - a part of Cultural Villages of Europe    recruitment of volunteers    coordination of transport    Group leader    SoMe

#### **EDUCATION**

2020-2022	Multimedia Design, Københavns Erhvervsakademi
	$\parallel$ Front-end design and programming $\parallel$ User Experience (UX) $\parallel$
	Content production    Busines    Technology
2016-2018	Kommunikationskurser, University of Southern Denmark
	$\parallel$ Corporate Communication $\parallel$ Multimodal tekstanalyse og – vurdering $\parallel$
	Multimodal tekstforfatning    Kommunikations- og kampagneplanlægning
	$\parallel$ Organisation og kulturanalyse $\parallel$ Kommunikation i en globaliseret verden $\parallel$
2013-2016	BA, International Business Communication - English and media,
	University of Southern Denmark
2015	Erasmus udveksling, Southampton Solent University (1 semester)

#### IT

12345	SoMe
12345	Microsoft Office
12345	Presentations in Prezi and PowerPoint
12345	Adobe Photoshop, -Illustrator, and -InDesign
12345	Production of newsletters in Mailchimp and Presscloud Vocast
12345	frontend design in HTML, CSS and Javascript
12345	UX- and UI design

## **FREE TIME AND HOBBIES**

In my freetime I love to be creative and I often experiment with new projects and materials. My friends and I enjoy playing board games, cooking and watching movies when we are together. Every other weekend I play Dungeons and Dragons online.